Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward Harriman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Administrative File, 1973-1993 (Box II:79-II:140)
  - Volunteers, 1981-1990
- Part II: Project File, 1976-1992 (Box II:140-II:205)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial records, briefings, research files, photographs, lists, press releases and clippings, and printed matter relating to major projects undertaken by the Democrats for the 80's.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of project and thereunder alphabetically by topic or type of material.
  - Democratic Campaign '84: Senate Research Projects, 1983 (Box II:140)
    - Administrative binder
    - Reports
      - Colorado, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:141, Box II:142)
      - Illinois, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:143)
      - Maine, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:144)
      - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box II:145)
      - New Hampshire, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:146)
  - Democratic Fact Book
    - 1982 edition
      - Consultants
      - Contributions, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, (5 folders)
      - Distribution, (10 folders) (Box II:147)
      - Drafts and updates, (3 folders)
      - Expenses
      - Press, (6 folders) (Box II:148)
      - Printed copies, final version, (2 folders)
      - Printing, (2 folders) (Box II:149)
      - Prospectus
    - 1984 edition
      - Contributions, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Distribution
      - Drafts
      - Historical binder
      - Press
      - Printed copy, final version, and draft, (1 folder) (Box II:150)
      - Selected documents
    - 1986 edition
      - Chapters, (9 folders); (13 folders); (11 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:151, Box II:152, Box II:153)
      - Consultants, (2 folders) (Box II:154)
      - Contributions, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, (4 folders)
      - Distribution, (5 folders); (8 folders) (Box II:155)
      - Editing, (3 folders)
      - Meetings
      - Miscellany
      - Notes (Box II:156)
      - Press, (5 folders)
      - Printed copies and text, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:157)
      - Printing
      - Promotion
      - Writers and reviewers
    - 1988 edition (proposed)
  - Democratic Satellite Fund
    - Background, 1980-1987
    - Brochure, 1987
    - Democratic National Convention
      - Democratic Convention Network, 1987-1988, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:158)
      - Kirk, Paul G., 1987-1988
      - Needs assessment survey, 1988
      - Notes, circa 1988
    - Direct mail, 1987
    - Financial records, 1987-1988
    - General correspondence and memoranda, 1985-1988, undated, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:159)
    - Notes, circa 1987-1988
  - Direct mail projects
    - 1982 election
      - Direct mail by Democrats for the 80's, (12 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:160)
      - Direct mail received from others, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:161)
      - Financial materials
        - Corporate refunds
        - Costs
        - Post office expenditures
        - Returns
        - Statements for services
        - Vendor invoices, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:162)
      - Membership requests
      - Memoranda, (2 folders)
      - Reports
      - Vendors and consultants, (1 folder); (8 folders) (Box II:163)
    - Win the Senate '84
      - Advisory board
      - Direct mail by Democrats for the 80's, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box II:164)
      - Direct mail received from others
      - Memoranda
      - Press releases
      - Stationary design
    - Senate Majority '86
      - Direct mail by Democrats for the 80's, (3 folders); (19 folders) (Box II:165, Box II:166)
      - Direct mail received from others
      - Individual and partnership receipts
      - Mailing and donor lists, (5 folders)
      - Memoranda, (2 folders)
      - Reports (Box II:167)
      - Stationary design
      - Summaries and event logs
      - Vendor invoices and payments
      - Vendors and consultants, (2 folders)
    - Democratic President '88
    - Pro-choice Democrats
  - Media campaigns
    - 1981, (2 folders)
    - 1982, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:168)
    - 1983, (3 folders)
    - 1984, (1 folder); (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:169, Box II:170)
    - 1985
    - 1988, (2 folders) (Box II:171)
  - National Polling Project
    - General file
      - Briefings, 1989
      - Center for National Policy, 1989
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box II:172)
      - Democratic Caucus issues conference, 1989
      - Democratic governors' conference, 1989
      - Democrats for the 80's polling, 1980-1983, (2 folders)
      - Expenditures, 1989-1990
      - Fund-raising, 1988-1990, (5 folders) (Box II:173)
      - Harriman Communication Center, 1989
      - House leadership briefing, 1989
      - Memoranda, 1989-1990
      - Notes and other writings, 1989-1990 (Box II:174)
      - Other polls, 1982-1990, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:175)
      - Presidential debates conference, 1989
      - Press clippings, 1989-1990, (4 folders)
      - Press releases, 1989-1990
      - Project overview, 1989
      - Social security tax rate cut, 1990
      - Virginia absentee ballot program, 1989
      - Westfield International Conference Center, 1989 (Box II:176)
    - Pollsters, analysts, and consultants
      - Bid specifications, 1989
      - Fingerhut, Vic, 1981-1985
      - Lists, 1989
      - Memoranda and notes, 1989
      - Napolitan, Joseph, 1989
      - Polling fees, 1989-1990
      - Pollsters' contracts and consulting agreements, 1989
      - Proposals, 1989
      - Rejected proposals, 1989, (1 folder) (Box II:177)
    - Projects
      - Campaign finance reform poll, 1989, (3 folders)
      - Campaign planning survey, 1990, (4 folders)
      - Capital gains tax cut focus groups, 1989, (3 folders) (Box II:178)
      - Drugs and crime survey, 1989, (2 folders)
      - First nationwide poll, 1989, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:179)
      - Focus group on politics, 1989
      - Medicare catastrophic coverage study, 1989, (4 folders) (Box II:180)
      - National election survey, 1990, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:181)
      - National ethics survey, 1989
      - National message project
        - Briefings, 1989, (3 folders)
        - Focus groups, 1989, (2 folders) (Box II:182)
        - General files, 1989-1990
        - National theme poll, 1989, (3 folders) (Box II:183, Box II:184, Box II:185)
        - Press clippings, 1990
        - Press release, 1990 (Box II:186)
      - National open-ended survey, 1990, (5 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:187)
      - Second national poll, 1989 (Box II:188)
      - Strategy memorandum and Democratic themes, 1989-1990
  - New Right manual
    - Background
      - Advertisements, 1979-1981
      - Articles, 1979-1982, (4 folders)
      - Christian Voice, 1979-1981
      - Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress, 1977-1981
      - Conservative Caucus, 1981
      - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee reports, 1977-1980
      - Fund for a conservative majority, 1980-1981
      - Fund-raising, 1981-1982
      - General correspondence and forwarded material, 1979-1982
      - Helms, Jesse, and the Congressional Club, 1976-1981 (Box II:189)
      - Liberty Lobby, 1981
      - Mid-America Conservative Political Action Committee, 1982
      - Moral Majority, 1979-1981, (2 folders)
      - National Conservative Foundation, 1981
      - National Conservative Political Action Committee
        - Church, Frank, 1979-1981
        - Eagleton, Tom, 1980-1981
        - General
          - 1977-1981, (3 folders)
          - 1982, undated (Box II:190)
        - Sarbanes, Paul, 1980-1981
        - Target '80, 1979-1980
      - Nightline transcript, 1980
      - Viguerie, Richard A., 1980-1981
    - Compilation of documents on the New Right, 1981-1984, (3 folders)
    - Manual, 1981 (Box II:191)
      - Drafts, (2 folders)
      - Printed copy
    - Memoranda, 1984
    - New York Time s advertisement
    - Press mailing list, 1981
  - Ninetieth birthday celebration for W. Averrell Harriman
    - Biographical information and research, 1981
    - Booklet, 1981, (2 folders)
    - Congressional Record, 1981
    - Correspondence
      - Alphabetical file, 1981, (3 folders)
      - Birthday cards and letters, 1981, (5 folders) (Box II:192)
      - Contributors, 1981
      - General, 1981-1982, (2 folders); (8 folders) (Box II:193)
      - Mailgram to celebrities, 1981
      - Regrets, 1981, (2 folders) (Box II:194)
      - Thank-you letters
        - Alphabetical file, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
        - Sent by
          - Harriman, Pamela, 1981
          - Harriman, W. Averell, 1981 (Box II:195)
      - VIP, 1981
    - Dinner committees, 1981, (3 folders)
    - Financial records
      - Daily financial summary sheets, 1981-1982
      - Federal Election Commission reports, 1981-1982, (4 folders)
      - General, 1981-1982 (Box II:196)
      - Pledges, 1981-1982
    - Photographs, 1981, (3 folders)
    - Planning
      - Auxiliary events, 1981
        - 21 Club, New York, N.Y., luncheon, Oct. 28
        - Boggs, Lindy, post-dinner party, Nov. 11
        - Corman, Jim, dinner, Nov. 10
        - Harriman brunch, Nov. 12
        - Haussaman, Carol W., reception, Oct. 28
        - Kraft, Joseph, and Ben H. Read luncheon, Nov. 18
        - Labor luncheon, Oct. 13
        - Ladies' luncheon
        - Pre-dinner reception, Nov. 11
        - Schedule
        - Wall Street, New York, N.Y., breakfast, Oct. 21
      - Binders
        - No. 1, 1981-1982
        - No. 2, 1981
        - No. 3, 1981 (Box II:197)
      - Complementary and reduced-price tickets, 1981
      - Head-table backdrop mural, 1981-1982
      - Hotel ballroom and site arrangements, 1981
      - Hotel room accommodations, 1981
      - Invitation design, 1981, (2 folders)
      - Labor, 1981
      - Legal memoranda, 1981
      - Lists
        - Attendees, 1981
        - Contributions, 1981
        - Invitees, 1981
        - Miscellaneous fund-raising and other lists, 1977-1981, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box II:198)
        - Suggested invitees, 1981
        - Telephone call and working lists, 1979-1981, (3 folders) (Box II:199)
        - Traditional Democratic contributors, 1980
      - Meetings and memoranda, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
      - Menu, 1981
      - Notes, 1981-1982, (3 folders)
      - Program, 1981 (Box II:200)
      - Safran, Lucia, workbook, 1981
      - "Save the date" postcard, 1981
      - Staffing and volunteers, 1981
      - Tables and seating, 1981, (2 folders)
    - Press
      - Clippings, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
      - Lists, 1980-1981
      - Memoranda and press packet, 1981
  - Party of the Decade, Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, Washington, D.C., 1990
    - Account balances, (2 folders)
    - Advertising (Box II:201)
    - Allocations and disbursements
    - Brunch
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional responses
    - Consultants
    - Contribution reports, (2 folders)
    - Democratic Decade project, 1989-1992
    - Entertainers, (2 folders)
    - Estimated budgets
    - Federal Election Commission report, (3 folders) (Box II:202)
    - Fund-raising agreement
    - Governor responses
    - Harriman family and guests
    - Insurance
    - Invitation
      - Designs
      - Lists, (2 folders)
      - Responses (Box II:203)
    - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts
    - Max out lists
    - Menu
    - Miscellany
    - Photographs, (3 folders)
    - Planning, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:204)
    - Pledges and commitments
    - Press
    - Press releases
    - Prospective entertainers
    - Publicity
    - Receipts
    - Seat pricing
    - Seating reports
    - Senate
      - Administrative assistants
      - Responses
      - Wives
    - Solicitations, (1 folder) (Box II:205)
    - Stagebill
    - Thank-you letters
    - Watergate Hotel
- Part II: Event File, 1978-1992 (Box II:205-II:262)
  Correspondence; memoranda; lists of invitees, attendees, and contributions; invitations; programs; agenda; notes; photographs; seating charts; speeches; publicity material; and news clippings.
  Arranged chronologically by date of event.
  - 1978, miscellaneous events (Box II:205)
  - 1979
    - Apr. 6, Tip O'Neill luncheon, New York, N.Y.
    - May 9, Democratic Congressional Dinner
      - Biographies
      - Call list
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:206)
      - Lists
      - Planning, (3 folders)
      - Tours
    - Miscellaneous events, (2 folders)
  - 1980 (Box II:207)
    - Apr. 22, White House Preservation Fund reception
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1981
    - Jan. 21, Democratic Dinner
    - Mar. 18, Woman's Suburban Democratic Club luncheon
    - Mar. 19, budget issue evening
    - Mar. 31, economy issue evening
    - Apr. 14, foreign policy issue evening
    - Apr. 30, economy issue evening
    - May 5, defense issue evening
    - May 19, tax policy issue evening
    - May 28, Chicago, Ill., fund-raising dinner, (2 folders)
    - June 2, energy issue evening
    - June 9, garden party, (1 folder) (Box II:208)
    - June 16, Robert S. Strauss and S. Lee Kling reception
    - Sept. 15, economy issue evening
    - Oct. 13, labor luncheon
    - Oct. 21, Wall Street breakfast
    - Oct., W. Averell Harriman birthday party planning
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1982
    - Jan. 28, defense and arms control issue evening
    - Mar. 4, Bruce Babbitt fund-raiser (Box II:209)
    - Mar. 9, Democratic agenda issue evening
    - Mar. 15, Paul Sarbanes reception
    - Apr. 1, budget alternatives issue evening
    - Apr. 19, budget and telecommunications issue evening
    - Apr. 22, congressional candidates reception
    - Apr. 26, San Francisco, Calif., reception, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:210)
    - May 6, new federalism issue evening
    - May 10, business community issue evening
    - May 11, American Israel Public Affairs Committee dinner
    - June 1, Walter F. Mondale issue evening
    - June 9, garden party, (2 folders)
    - June 15, District of Columbia Democratic State Committee reception
    - June 23, Madeline Kunin reception (Box II:211)
    - June 24-27, National Party Conference
    - June 29, Edward M. Kennedy issue evening
    - July 4, Willow Oaks picnic
    - July 23, VIP press reception
    - Sept. 1, Wall Street Club reception
    - Sept. 14, Middle East issue evening
    - Sept. 19, Tom Bradley issue evening
    - Sept. 21, economy issue evening
    - Sept. 23, Harriett Woods reception
    - Oct. 1, Broadway brunch with stars, (2 folders) (Box II:212)
    - Oct. 6, Jim Howard reception
    - Oct. 8, coffee at Harriman home
    - Oct. 10, Dick Davis reception
    - Oct. 26, ambassador reception
    - Oct., Dallas, Tex., and New York, N.Y., fund-raisers, (3 folders)
    - Nov. 2, election night, (2 folders) (Box II:213)
    - Dec. 1, newly-elected Democratic members of Congress reception
    - Dec. 9, election assessment issue evening
    - Dec. 14, Bill Bradley reception
    - Dec. 15, 98th Congress agenda issue evening
    - Dec., political action committee dinners
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1983
    - Feb. 28, Democratic Celebration honoring Democratic governors
      - Contributions, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence (Box II:214)
      - Federal Election Commission reports, (2 folders)
      - Lists
      - Photographs
      - Planning, (3 folders)
      - Press (Box II:215)
      - Seating, (2 folders)
      - Speeches
    - Mar. 8, energy and natural gas policy issue evening
    - Mar. 10, Salute to San Francisco, Calif.
    - Mar. 22, recovery and industrial policy issue evening
    - Apr. 13, trade policy issue evening
    - Apr. 21, Victor Borge brunch, (2 folders)
    - Apr. 23, Jefferson-Jackson day breakfast (Box II:216)
    - Apr. 28, labor and management relations issue evening
    - May 1-2, Alabama and Mississippi fund-raising
      - Altmayer, Jay P., dinner
      - Correspondence
      - Planning
      - Press
      - Speeches
    - May 12, Jim Hunt reception (Box II:217)
    - May 23, Economy '83 and '84 issue evening
    - June 20, Walter F. Mondale issue evening
    - June 24, garden party, (2 folders)
    - July 27, Solomon Ortiz reception
    - Aug. 24, Wall Street Club luncheon
    - Sept. 14, Mario M. Cuomo issue evening
    - Sept. 20, Edward M. Kennedy issue evening
    - Sept. 26, Dan Rostenkowski issue evening (Box II:218)
    - Sept. 29, Tony Randall brunch, (2 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec., Presidential Sweep events
    - Oct. 4, John Glenn issue evening
    - Oct. 11, Bill Allain reception
    - Oct. 17, Edwin Edwards reception, (2 folders)
    - Oct. 19, Ernest F. ("Fritz") Hollings issue dinner
    - Oct. 26, Gary Hart issue evening (Box II:219)
    - Nov. 2, Robert S. Strauss and Andrew Young issue evening
    - Nov. 9, Alan Cranston issue evening
    - Dec. 5, Presidential Trust dinner
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence
      - Lists
      - Planning, (2 folders)
      - Seating
      - Speech
    - Dec. 14, John D. Rockefeller, IV, reception (Box II:220)
      - Background information
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence
      - Lists
      - Planning
      - Seating
      - Slides
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1984
    - Feb. 25, governors' wives luncheon
    - Feb. 27, Salute to Democratic Governors (Box II:221)
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence
      - Lists
      - Planning, (3 folders)
      - Seating
    - Mar. 1, William F. Winter reception
    - Mar. 15, foreign policy issue evening (Box II:222)
    - Mar. 24, Gridiron Club dinner
    - Mar. 26, District of Columbia Democratic State Committee dinner
    - Mar. 28, luncheon
    - Apr. 9, John Glenn planning committee
    - Apr. 10, domestic policy issue evening
    - May 9, Andrew Young reception
    - May 12, James Hunt reception
    - May 15, William Milfred Batten luncheon
    - May 24, Lowell Leberman reception
    - May 30, Seafarers International convention
    - June 8, garden party, (2 folders)
    - June 10, John D. Rockefeller, IV, reception
    - June 12, Thomas S. Foley luncheon
    - June 14, William F. Winter reception
    - June 19, Carl Levin fund-raiser
    - June 20, Democratic Convention issue evening
    - July 16-19, Democratic National Convention (Box II:223)
      - Correspondence
      - Invitations
      - Lists
      - Miscellaneous
      - Photographs
      - Planning
      - Press, (2 folders)
      - Promotional material
      - Speeches
    - Sept. 11, Al Gore reception (Box II:224)
    - Sept. 13, Joan Growe reception, (2 folders)
    - Sept. 18, Tom Hayden and Jane Fonda reception
    - Sept. 21, fall garden party
    - Sept. 25, Lloyd Doggett reception
    - Oct. 2, Mario M. Cuomo luncheon
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence
      - Lists
      - Planning
      - Seating (Box II:225)
      - Speeches
    - Oct. 3, Tom Harkin reception
    - Oct. 21, Loudoun County Democrats harvest dinner
    - Oct. 24, John D. Rockefeller, IV, luncheon
    - Nov. 6, election night party
    - Nov. 26, Mario M. Cuomo second anniversary celebration
    - Nov. 29 Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee reception
    - Dec. 12, issue evening meeting
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1985
    - Jan. 28, Association of State Democratic Executive Directors meeting
    - Mar. 18, Paul G. Kirk reception, (1 folder) (Box II:226)
    - Apr. 24, Washington, D.C., Senate Majority '86 dinner
      - Breakfast
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Lists
      - Photographs
      - Planning, (2 folders)
      - Press (Box II:227)
      - Seating
      - Speeches
    - May 1, Cancer Ball reception
    - May 7, Richard A. Gephardt issue evening
    - May 16, Les Aspin issue evening
    - June 5, Riitta Haley luncheon
    - June 11, Alan Cranston reception
    - June 14, New York garden party
    - June 18, Bill Gray issue evening, (2 folders)
    - June 22, Los Angeles, Calif., Senate Majority '86 dinner (Box II:228)
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence
      - Lists
      - Planning, (2 folders)
      - Press
      - Speeches
    - June 26, Christopher J. Dodd reception
    - Sept. 11, Mary Sue Terry fund-raiser
    - Sept. 22, Tony Coelho reception (Box II:229)
    - Sept. 23, Gerald L. Baliles reception
    - Sept. 29, "An Afternoon in the Country"
    - Oct. 1, Harriett Woods reception
    - Oct. 2, Dan Rostenkowski issue evening, (2 folders)
    - Oct. 8, Gary Hart reception
    - Oct. 9, Democratic National Committee gala
    - Oct. 11, garden and house tour
    - Oct. 16, Women Making History, (1 folder) (Box II:230)
    - Oct. 18, Chicago, Ill., Senate Majority '86 dinner, (4 folders)
    - Oct. 24, Bill Bradley issue evening
    - Oct. 29, Dale Bumpers reception
    - Nov. 4, John V. Evans reception (Box II:231)
    - Nov. 7, Sam Nunn issue evening, (2 folders)
    - Nov. 13, Texas regional political action committee dinner
    - Nov. 21, John Breaux reception
    - Dec. 4, John Glenn reception
    - Dec. 9, New York, N.Y., Senate Majority '86 dinner
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Planning, (2 folders) (Box II:232)
      - Press
      - Seating, (2 folders)
      - Speech
    - Dec. 19, Christmas luncheon
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1986
    - Jan. 27, labor luncheon, (2 folders)
    - Jan. 29, Patrick J. Leahy reception, (2 folders)
    - Feb. 25, Bob Graham reception, (2 folders) (Box II:233)
    - Apr. 8, Ed Garvey reception
    - Apr. 8, Thomas Daschle reception, (2 folders)
    - Apr. 15, Jess Hay reception
    - Apr. 22, Senate Majority '86 dinner
      - Contributions, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:234)
      - Correspondence, (3 folders)
      - Kentucky Derby box auction
      - Lists, (2 folders)
      - Nightcap reception
      - Planning, (2 folders) (Box II:235)
      - Planning binder, (3 folders)
      - Press
      - Seating, (1 folder) (Box II:236)
      - Speeches
    - Apr. 29, Tim Wirth reception
    - May 1, Jim Jones reception
    - May 7, Joseph R. Biden issue evening, (2 folders)
    - May 12, Brock Adams reception
    - May 14, Harry Reid reception
    - May 15, Rudy Perpich reception
    - May-June, issue evenings, (2 folders) (Box II:237)
    - June 3, Kent Conrad reception
    - June 5, Alan J. Dixon reception
    - June 11, Daniel K. Inouye issue evening, (2 folders)
    - June 18, Alan Cranston reception
    - June 20, garden party, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:238)
    - June 23, Thomas S. Foley reception
    - June 24, Jim Wright issue evening, (2 folders)
    - July 2, Marion Barry reception
    - Sept. 15, John Milliken reception
    - Sept. 29, Senate Majority '86 luncheon, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:239)
    - Nov. 4, election night
    - Dec. 11, "N" Street dinner
  - 1987
    - Feb. 2, labor union reception
    - Feb. 4, Preston Tisch reception
    - Feb. 10, James Wright reception, (2 folders)
    - May 7, "An Evening with Clark Clifford"
    - June 3, satellite fund-raising dinner
      - Binder, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:240)
      - Contributions, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, (3 folders)
      - Lists, (1 folder) (Box II:241)
      - Miscellany, (2 folders)
      - Photographs
      - Planning, (3 folders)
      - Press (Box II:242)
      - Seating, (2 folders)
      - Speeches
    - July 29, Democratic Governors' Association meeting, (2 folders)
    - Sept. 9, evening with Al Gore
    - Oct. 14, George J. Mitchell reception (Box II:243)
    - Oct. 21, evening with Paul Simon (1928-2003)
    - Dec. 2, evening with Jesse Jackson
    - Dec. 9, evening with Richard A. Gephardt
    - Miscellaneous events
  - 1988
    - Mar. 29, Association for a Better New York breakfast
    - Mar. 31, Tipper Gore luncheon
    - Apr. 12, Al Gore dinner, New York, N.Y.
    - Apr. 14, Reubin Askew reception
    - Apr. 20, annual political action committee dinner